Finding Aid for the Kenneth Rexroth Papers LSC.0175
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 6: Printed materials, 1936-1976; 36 boxes (18 linear ft.).
  - Subseries 6C: Ephemera,., 1940-1974; 10 boxes.
    - Wilson, John., no date.; 1 item. (Box 128, Folder 13)
      On the way to the ruins at Palenque (Long Beach, NY: Doggerel Press).
    - Wine., no date.; 3 items. (Box 128, Folder 14)
      Assorted print materials.
    - Writers Group., no date.; 1 item. (Box 128, Folder 15)
    - Xalman., 1974 May.; 2 items. (Box 128, Folder 16)
      Chicano poetry group.
    - Zorach, William., 1969.; 1 item. (Box 128, Folder 17)
      Memorial exhibition program.
    - Zukofsky, Louis and Celia Thaew., no date.; 9 items. (Box 128, Folder 18)
      Music and words for "When is winter spring?" and other songs.
  - Subseries 6D: Little magazines,., 1936-1976; 8 boxes.
    Periodicals of limited circulation, devoted to poetry or avant-garde thinking. Arranged alphabetically by the title of the publication.
    - Aleph., 1976.; 1 item. (Box 128, Folder 19)
      Edited by L.R. Fox and Mel Raff; published in Takoma Park, MD (no. 3, reprint of Carlo Parcelli's Pillow Book)
    - Alkahest., 1968-1969.; 3 items. (Box 128, Folder 20)
      Assorted editors. Published in Middletown, CT by Wesleyan University Press (no. 1-3)
    - Alternative., 1948.; 2 items. (Box 128, Folder 21)
      Libertarian monthly; published in New York (v. 1, no. 1, 3)
    - Alternative Media Brochure., no date.; 1 item. (Box 128, Folder 22)
      Guide to alternative and avante-garde publications
    - American Pen (The)., 1970.; 1 item. (Box 129, Folder 1)
      Edited by Roger Dooley; published in New York by the P.E.N. American Center
    - American Revolutionary Pamphlets., no date.; 2 items. (Box 129, Folder 2)
      Essays and poetry (no. 1-2)
    - Anarchism., no date.; 1 item. (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - A[narchist] Newsletter., 1974 March.; 1 item. (Box 129, Folder 4)
      Published by the Anarchs of New York
    - Anthology of Underground Poetry., 1970.; 1 item. (Box 129, Folder 5)
      Edited by Herman Berlandt; published in Berkeley by Poets' Commune Publications (no. 7)
    - Apprentice., 1961.; 1 item. (Box 129, Folder 6)
      Edited by Nancy Tafaro; published by the San Francisco College for Women
    - Assembling., no date.; 2 items. (Box 129, Folder 7)
      Compiled by Richard Kostelanetz, Henry Korn, and Mike Metz; published in Brooklyn, NY (v. 2-3)
    - Beatitude., 1959 May.; 1 item. (Box 129, Folder 8)
      Assorted editors, published in San Francisco by John Kelly; includes a poem by Allen Ginsberg about Kenneth Rexroth (no. 3)
    - Beloit Poetry Journal (The)., 1955.; 1 item. (Box 129, Folder 9)
      Published in Beloit, WI by Beloit College (v. 5, no. 4)
    - Big Boulevard., 1974.; 1 item. (Box 129, Folder 10)
      Edited and published in Long Beach, CA by William J. Robson (v. 2, no. 3)
    - Black and Red., 1967.; 1 item. (Box 129, Folder 11)
      Published in San Francisco by Polytechnic Senior High School; includes Mary Rexroth's first published poem (v. 1, no. 1)
    - Black Bart Brigade., 1971 November.; 1 item. (Box 129, Folder 12)
      Edited and published by Irv Thomas in Canyon, CA (no. 1)
    - Black Flag., 1965.; 6 items. (Box 129, Folder 13)
      Published in San Francisco by the Institute for Social Thought for El Movemiento Nacionalista Revolución Negra (no. 4-9)
    - Blackfish., 1972-1973.; 1 item. (Box 129, Folder 14)
      Edited by B.T. Brett and Allan Safarik; published in B.C., Canada (no. 4-5)
    - Book Review (The)., 1971.; 3 items. (Box 129, Folder 15)
      Edited by Jay Bail; published in San Francisco by J.B. Goncharsky. Features an interview with Kenneth Rexroth (no. 15, 18)
    - Bulletin of the Committee for Non-Violent Revolution., 1946.; 4 items. (Box 129, Folder 16)
      Published in San Francisco (no. 7-9)
    - Bulletin of the Hudson Book Club., no date.; 1 item. (Box 129, Folder 17)
      Published in New York; includes commentary by Rexroth on erotic Chinese novel (v. 9, no. 108)
    - Caim., 1974.; 1 item. (Box 129, Folder 18)
      Edited by Bernard Taylor, Muriel C. Ashley, and James Taylor; published in Baltimore, Maryland (v. 2, no. 1)
    - Caryatid., no date.; 1 item. (Box 130, Folder 1)
      Edited by Gail White in New Orleans, LA
    - Caw! magazine., 1968 May-June.; 1 item. (Box 130, Folder 2)
      Published in New York by Students for a Democratic Society (no. 2)
    - Chrysalis Review., 1962.; 1 item. (Box 130, Folder 3)
      Assorted editors; published in San Francisco (no. 2)
    - C.I.R.A. Bulletin., 1971-1972.; 2 items. (Box 130, Folder 4)
      Published by the Centre International de Recherches sur l'Anarchisme (no. 22, 24)
    - Club Sento., 1957-1964.; 4 items. (Box 130, Folder 5)
      Japanese-language poetry publication published in Osaka (no. 29, 31, 36, 38)
    - Coda., 1974 April.; 1 item. (Box 130, Folder 6)
      Published in New York by Poets and Writers, INC. (v. 1, no. 5)
    - Combustion., 1958 April.; 2 items. (Box 130, Folder 7)
      Poetry review published in Toronto by the Contact Press. Includes "Homage to Rexroth" by Kenneth McRobbie (no. 6)
    - CQ., 1980.; 1 item. (Box 130, Folder 8)
      Published by the California State Poetry Society (v. 7, no 2)
    - Despite Everything., 1963, 1969.; 2 items. (Box 130, Folder 9)
      Published in Berkeley (v. 1, no. 1; v. 4 no. 2)
    - Dialectics., 1962 April.; 1 item. (Box 130, Folder 10)
      Published in San Francisco by the Catholic Committee for Democratic Socialism
    - Eikon., 1967.; 1 item. (Box 130, Folder 11)
      Edited by Robert Fay and Malcolm Schade; published in Portsmouth, NH (v. 1, no. 1)
    - E-mir., 1951 December.; 1 item. (Box 130, Folder 12)
      Japanese-language poetry, critique, and fiction (no. 1)
    - Enquiry., 1945.; 1 item. (Box 130, Folder 13)
      Journal of independent radical thought (v. 2, no. 3)
    - Extantis., 1958-1959.; 2 items. (Box 130, Folder 14)
      Edited by Jason Smith; published in San Francisco (no. 1-2)
    - Friends of Yvan Goll Bulletin., 1953.; 2 items. (Box 130, Folder 15)
      Poetry review published in Berkeley (no. 1-2)
    - Gallimaufry., 1975.; 2 items. (Box 130, Folder 16)
      Poetry, fiction and graphics magazine edited and published in San Francisco by Mary MacArthur
    - Ginga., no date.; 1 item. (Box 130, Folder 17)
      Japanese-language magazine of poetry and fairy tales, with illustrations (no. 10)
    - Gravida., 1973.; 1 item. (Box 130, Folder 18)
      Edited by Romaine Murphy and Lynne Savitt; published in New York by the Women's Poetry Collective
    - Greensboro Review (The)., 1971.; 1 item. (Box 130, Folder 19)
      Assorted editors, published by the University of North Carolina at Greensboro (no. 9)
    - Hampden-Sydney Poetry Review., 1975.; 2 items. (Box 131, Folder 1)
      Formerly Maryland Poetry Review; published in Virginia
    - Harpoem., no date.; 1 item. (Box 131, Folder 2)
      Japanese-language poetry magazine published by the Kyoto Artist Club Press
    - Holocene Gazette and Country Traveller., 1970.; 1 item. (Box 131, Folder 3)
      Radical ecology newsletter, published in Vermont
    - Hotcha!., 1969.; 9 items. (Box 131, Folder 4)
      German-language avant-garde publication
    - Hyperion., 1970-1973.; 5 items. (Box 131, Folder 5)
      Assorted editors; published in Berkeley by the Thorp Springs Press (v. 3, no. 1, 9, 11)
    - I Think I Hear Camels Coming., 1966-1972.; 5 items. (Box 131, Folder 6)
      Formerly Camels Coming Newsletter and/or The Camel's Hump; edited and published in San Francisco by Richard Morris (no. 2, 4-6)
    - In Fact., 1940 June.; 1 item. (Box 131, Folder 7)
      Edited by George Seldes; published in New York by In Fact, INC. (v. 1, no. 2)
    - Intrepid., 1971-1972.; 3 items. (Box 131, Folder 8)
      Assorted editors; published in New York by Allen de Loach (no. 20, 23-24)
    - Invisible City., 1972-1975.; 7 items. (Box 131, Folder 9-10)
      Edited by John McBride and Paul Vangelisti; published by the Red Hill Press in Fairfax, CA (no. 5-8, 13-17)
    - Isthmus., ca. 1975.; 1 item. (Box 132, Folder 1)
      Edited by J. Rutherford Willems; published in San Francisco by the Isthmus Press (no. 4)
    - Jeopardy., 1969 April.; 1 item. (Box 132, Folder 2)
      Edited by Ted Shields; published in Bellingham by the Associated Student Body of Western Washington State College (v. 5)
    - Joglars., 1964.; 1 item. (Box 132, Folder 3)
      Assorted editors; published in Providence, RI (v. 1, no. 1)
    - Journal for the Protection of all Beings., 1968.; 2 items. (Box 132, Folder 4)
      On the barricades: revolution and depression. Published in San Francisco by Beach Books and City Lights Books (no. 2)
    - Kayak., 1968-1970.; 7 items. (Box 132, Folder 5-6)
      Edited by George Hitchcock; published in San Francisco (no. 2, 13, 18-19, 21- 22, 24)
    - Kyoto Review (The)., 1975.; 1 item. (Box 132, Folder 7)
      Edited by Yuzuru Katagiri and Osamu Ono; published in Kyoto, Japan by the Kyoto Seika College Press (no. 6)
    - Kyoto Seika English Papers (The)., 1975.; 2 items. (Box 132, Folder 8)
      Edited by Yuzuru Katagiri and Osamu Ono; published in Kyoto, Japan by the Kyoto Seika College Press (no. 5)
    - Las Siegas., 1969.; 1 item. (Box 132, Folder 9)
      Published by the University of California, Santa Barbara, Letters and Science Scholars Program (v. 1)
    - Left/Right Digest., 1970 July-August.; 1 item. (Box 132, Folder 10)
      Published by the Trends Analyses Division, American Jewish Committee (v. 3, no. 7)
    - Little Square Review (The)., 1972.; 1 item. (Box 133, Folder 1)
      Edited by John Ridland; published in Santa Barbara, CA (no. 9-10)
    - Living Hand., 1975.; 1 item. (Box 133, Folder 2)
      Assorted editors; published in Weston, CT (no. 4)
    - Local Tenderness., 1974.; 1 item. (Box 133, Folder 3)
      Published in East Lansing, MI by the Old Marble Press
    - Man-root., 1970.; 1 item. (Box 133, Folder 4)
      Edited by Paul Mariah and Richard Tagget; published in San Francisco by Paul Mariah (no. 3)
    - Matrix., 1973.; 1 item. (Box 133, Folder 5)
      Anthology of women's poetry, edited by Idell; published in Los Angeles, CA by Charm (v. 3)
    - Menckeniana., 1963-1964.; 3 items. (Box 133, Folder 6)
      Published in Baltimore (Enoch Pratt Free Library). Includes letters regarding Rexroth poetry from Betty Adler.
    - Mirrors Magazine., no date.; 2 items. (Box 133, Folder 7)
      Published in Elmhurst, Ill. by York Community High School (v. 14, no. 1)
    - Mouth Magazine., 1974.; 4 items. (Box 133, Folder 8)
      Edited by John Staley; published in Buffalo, NY (v. 1, no. 6; v. 2, no. 1)
    - Naked Ear (The)., no date.; 1 item. (Box 133, Folder 9)
      Published in Taos, NM (no. 5)
    - New Orleans Review., 1974.; 1 item. (Box 133, Folder 10)
      Published in New Orleans by Loyola University (v. 4, no. 1)
    - NHK., 1975.; 2 items. (Box 133, Folder 11)
      Japanese and English-language publication by the Japanese Broadcasting Corporation; features poetry and interview of Kenneth Rexroth on p. 48 (no. 6)
    - Notebook (The)., 1936 November.; 1 item. (Box 133, Folder 12)
      Edited by Flozari Rockwood; published in Cleveland, Ohio by the Pegasus Press (v. 3, no. 4)
    - Om., 1974.; 2 items. (Box 133, Folder 13)
      Japanese and English-language publication focusing on environmental issues, such as saving Suwanose Island (no. 10, and an undetermined issue)
    - Open Places., 1975-1976.; 1 item. (Box 133, Folder 14)
      Edited by Eleanor M. Bender; published in Columbia, MS by the Stephens College Department of English (no. 19-20)
    - Other Scenes., 1973-1974.; 2 items. (Box 133, Folder 15)
      Edited and published by John Wilcock in New York. See Series 6, Subseries 6E (Newspapers) for newspaper format of same title
    - Paintbrush., 1975.; 1 item. (Box 133, Folder 16)
      Edited by B.M. Bennani; published in Laramie, WY by Ishtar Publications, INC (no. 4)
    - Panache., 1971-1973.; 3 items. (Box 134, Folder 1)
      Edited by David R. Lenson; published in Princeton, NJ by R.B. Frank (no. 8, 11-12)
    - Personals., 1963.; 1 item. (Box 134, Folder 2)
      Published in Pacifica, CA by Communique; personal ads for women and men
    - Pharaoh Phunnies., no date.; 1 item. (Box 134, Folder 3)
      Underground comic
    - Ploughshares., 1975.; 1 item. (Box 134, Folder 4)
      Assorted editors; published in Boston. Includes poems by Kenneth Rexroth (v. 2, no. 3)
    - Poet., 1968.; 2 items. (Box 134, Folder 5)
      Assorted editors; published in Madras, India by the World Poetry Society (Maltese and New Zealand issues)
    - Poets Yeggs and Thirsties., 1975.; 2 items. (Box 134, Folder 6)
      Edited by Caedmon Literature; printed at the New England Free Press in MA (v. 1, no. 1)
    - Poetry Exchange., 1975.; 2 items. (Box 134, Folder 7)
      Japanese-language poetry publication with notes on authors in English. Includes mention of Carol Tinker (no. 2)
    - Poetry Magazine., 1967 June.; 1 item. (Box 134, Folder 8)
      Assorted editors; published by the Poetry Society of Australia. Features poems by Rexroth on p. 20 (no. 3)
    - Polymus., 1969.; 1 item. (Box 134, Folder 9)
      Edited by Constantine Axiotis and John Lee (no. 1)
    - Quarry., 1972-1973.; 2 items. (Box 134, Folder 10)
      Assorted editors; published by the University of California, Santa Cruz (no. 2-3)
    - Quarterly., 1967.; 3 items. (Box 134, Folder 11)
      Edited by Paul Larsen; published in New Jersey by Montclair State College (v. 40, no. 1-2)
    - Quoz?., 1975.; 1 item. (Box 134, Folder 12)
      Edited by Carlo Giovanni Cicatelli; published in San Francisco by the Trinity Press (v. 3, no. 9)
    - Radicals in the Professions., 1968.; 1 item. (Box 134, Folder 13)
      Published in Ann Arbour, MI by the Radical Education Project. See also Something Else! (v. 1, no. 10)
    - Ravine., no date.; 5 items. (Box 134, Folder 14)
      Japanese-language magazine of poetry and prose (no. 44-46)
    - Recovering Literature., 1972.; 1 item. (Box 134, Folder 15)
      Assorted editors; published in La Jolla, CA (v. 1, no. 1)
    - Rekiteri., 1975.; 1 item. (Box 134, Folder 16)
      Japanese-language magazine (no. 198)
    - Right of Aesthetic Realism to be Known (The)., 1973-1974.; 9 items. (Box 134, Folder 17)
      Published in New York
    - Rising Generation (The)., 1975 December.; 1 item. (Box 135, Folder 1)
      Japanese-language publication featuring Kenneth Rexroth (no. 12)
    - Ronin., 1974 July.; 1 item. (Box 135, Folder 2)
      Joint issue with Phuen. Assorted editors, published in Japan (no. 15)
    - Salon des Sujets., 1974 November.; 1 item. (Box 135, Folder 3)
      Japanese-language publication (no. 32)
    - Sebastian Quill., 1970.; 1 item. (Box 135, Folder 4)
      Edited by James Mitchell; published in San Francisco (no. 1)
    - Second Coming., 1974, 1976.; 2 items. (Box 135, Folder 5)
      Edited and published by A.D. Winans in San Francisco (v. 3, no. 1-2; v. 4, no. 1-2)
    - Seizure Magazine., 1972.; 2 items. (Box 135, Folder 6)
      Assorted editors; published in Eugene, OR (v. 1, no. 1-2)
    - Shocks., 1973-1975.; 2 items. (Box 135, Folder 7)
      Edited by Stephen Vincent; published in San Francisco (no. 2, 5)
    - Simbolica., ca. 1953.; 2 items. (Box 135, Folder 8)
      Poetry review published in New York (no. 12, 19)
    - Sinter., 1975 September.; 1 item. (Box 135, Folder 9)
      Published by D.E. Steward in Switzerland (no. 8)
    - Small Press Review., 1974-1975.; 3 items. (Box 135, Folder 10)
      Books and reviews from the Something Else Press (no. 21, 24, 32)
    - Something Else!., 1969.; 3 items. (Box 135, Folder 11)
      Formerly Radicals in the Professions newsletter. Published in Ann Arbor, MI by the Radical Education Project (v. 2, no. 2, 4, 6)
    - Spectrum., 1970-1971.; 4 items. (Box 135, Folder 12)
      Published by the University of California, Santa Barbara (v. 12, no. 2; v. 13, no. 1-2)
    - Stooge., no date.; 1 item. (Box 135, Folder 13)
      Edited by Geoffrey Young and Laura Chester; published in Oconomowoc Lake, WI (no. 11)
    - Sun., 1974.; 1 item. (Box 135, Folder 14)
      Edited by Bill Zavatsky; published in New York (v. 4, no. 1)
    - Suppository., 1970.; 1 item. (Box 135, Folder 15)
      Edited by Eustache Trevache; published in Santa Barbara by Richard Kempton
    - The., no date.; 7 items. (Box 136, Folder 1)
      Poetry magazine published in Boulder, Co (numbered volumes 6-13)
    - Toothpick Lisbon and the Orcas Islands., 1971-1972.; 3 items. (Box 136, Folder 2)
      Edited and published in Seattle, WA by Michael Wiater
    - Tractor., 1974.; 3 items. (Box 136, Folder 3)
      Edited by Barbara Szerlip in San Francisco, CA (v. 5)
    - Transfer., 1960.; 2 items. (Box 136, Folder 4)
      Edited by Norman Moser; published by San Francisco State College (no. 10). Includes a humorous broadside related to Transfer no. 9, by David Deck.
    - Tukusi., 1972.; 1 item. (Box 136, Folder 5)
      Japanese-language publication (no. 9)
    - Uncle Saxophone Magazine (The)., no date.; 1 item. (Box 136, Folder 6)
      Published in Goleta, CA (no. 5)
    - Unmuzzled Ox., 1973-1975.; 3 items. (Box 136, Folder 7)
      Edited by Michael Andre; published in New York. Includes interview with Allen Ginsberg and work by Kenneth Rexroth (v. 2, no. 1-2, v. 3, no. 2)
    - Unspeakable Visions of the Individual., 1971-1973.; 2 items. (Box 136, Folder 8)
      Edited and published by Arthur and Glee Knight in California, PA (v. 1 no. 1; v. 3, no. 1-2
    - UT Review., 1973.; 1 item. (Box 136, Folder 9)
      Poetry anthology edited by Duane Locke; published in FL by the University of Tampa (v. 3 no. 1)
    - Vagabond., 1974-1975.; 3 items. (Box 136, Folder 10)
      Edited and published in Ellensburg, WA by John Bennett (no. 19-20)
    - Wormwood Review (The)., 1970.; 1 item. (Box 136, Folder 11)
      Edited by Marvin Malone; published in Stockton, CA (v. 10, no. 2)
  - Subseries 6E: Newspapers,., 1938-1975; 5 boxes.
    Loose newspapers found throughout the collection during the 2005 reprocessing, arranged alphabetically by the title of the publication. Includes socialist and anarchy- themed papers, student papers, and international papers.
    - American Poetry Review (The)., 1972.; 2 items. (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Argo., 1969 March.; 1 item. (Box 137, Folder 2)
      Student paper; article about Rexroth's UCSB contract renewal on p. 10
    - Asahi Evening News., 1972.; 1 item. (Box 137, Folder 3)
    - Brown Daily Herald., 1960.; 1 item. (Box 137, Folder 4)
      Supplement to the socialist newspaper
    - Chicago Tribune., 1973 June.; 1 item. (Box 137, Folder 5)
      Book World section on Midwestern authors
    - Chinese World., 1951.; 1 item. (Box 137, Folder 6)
      Chinese and English-language newspaper
    - Clear Creek., 1971.; 2 items. (Box 137, Folder 7)
      Environmental newspaper
    - Dagens Nyheter., 1958 June 17.; 1 item. (Box 137, Folder 8)
      Swedish newspaper
    - Daily Bruin., 1967.; 2 items. (Box 137, Folder 9)
      UCLA student paper
    - Der Krigsdienstgegner le Resistant a la guerre., 1971.; 1 item. (Box 137, Folder 10)
      German newspaper
    - El Gaucho., 1969-1970.; 49 items. (Box 137, Folder 11-14)
      UCSB student paper
    - For the time being., 1972.; 1 item. (Box 138, Folder 1)
      UCSB student ministry newspaper
    - Free University Coalition., 1968.; 1 item. (Box 138, Folder 2)
      UCSB student leftist publication
    - Freedom., 1953-1954.; 27 items. (Box 138, Folder 3)
      Anarchist newspaper
    - Golden Gater., 1954.; 1 item. (Box 138, Folder 4)
      San Francisco newspaper
    - Hotspur., 1969.; 2 items. (Box 138, Folder 5)
      Columbia University's summer literary newspaper
    - Indigena., 1974-1975.; 1 item. (Box 138, Folder 6)
      American Indian newspaper
    - Individual Action., 1953-1954.; 9 items. (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - Industrial Worker., 1964.; 1 item. (Box 138, Folder 8)
      World labor news
    - Intro Bulletin., 1956.; 1 item. (Box 138, Folder 9)
      Literary newspaper of the arts
    - Isla Vista Viewpoint., 1970-1971.; 3 items. (Box 138, Folder 10)
      Independent newspaper
    - It (1-4 of 5)., 1960, 1968-1969.; 15 items. (Box 138, Folder 11-14)
      Independent London paper
    - It (5 of 5)., 1969 August-September.; 3 items. (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Japan Times (The)., 1972.; 1 item. (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - Kaleidoscope., 1968-1969.; 14 items. (Box 139, Folder 3-5)
      Independent Milwaukee paper
    - La Obra., 1951.; 1 item. (Box 139, Folder 6)
      Buenos Aires newspaper
    - La Vanguardia., 1967.; 1 item. (Box 139, Folder 7)
      Spanish newspaper
    - Labor Action., 1940.; 1 item. (Box 139, Folder 8)
      Newspaper of the Workers Party
    - Literary Tabloid (The)., 1975.; 1 item. (Box 139, Folder 9)
    - Los Angeles Free Press., 1969.; 1 item. (Box 139, Folder 10)
    - Mainichi Daily News., 1972.; 1 item. (Box 139, Folder 11)
      Japanese newspaper
    - Manhattan Tribune., 1971.; 6 items. (Box 139, Folder 12)
      Independent New York Westside newspaper
    - Marianne., 1938.; 1 item. (Box 139, Folder 13)
      French newspaper with cover story on Aldous Huxley and images of Nazi Germany
    - Messiah's World Crusade Universal Communicator., no date.; 1 item. (Box 139, Folder 14)
      Commune paper
    - Muhammad Speaks., 1969 August.; 1 item. (Box 140, Folder 1)
      Independent African American paper
    - New York Free Press., 1968.; 3 items. (Box 140, Folder 2)
      Independent paper
    - News and Letters., 1969 November.; 1 item. (Box 140, Folder 3)
      Independent workers' paper
    - Nola Express., 1973.; 2 items. (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - Occidental (The)., 1973.; 2 items. (Box 140, Folder 5)
      Occidental College student paper
    - Other Scenes., no date.; 3 items. (Box 140, Folder 6)
      John Wilcock alternative newspaper
    - Pacific Sun., 1970.; 2 items. (Box 140, Folder 7)
      Includes a literary quarterly
    - Peace News., 1967.; 1 item. (Box 140, Folder 8)
    - Pirate Press., 1972.; 2 items. (Box 140, Folder 9)
      Ventura College student paper
    - Plug and Socket., 1969.; 1 item. (Box 140, Folder 10)
      Independent music paper
    - Poetry Now., no date.; 3 items. (Box 140, Folder 11)
      Poetry newspaper
    - Post (The)., 1971 January.; 1 item. (Box 140, Folder 12)
      University of Wisconsin, Madison student paper
    - Probe., 1969.; 9 items. (Box 140, Folder 13)
      Independent radical newspaper; includes stories related to UCSB
    - Revolutionary Youth Movement., no date.; 1 item. (Box 140, Folder 14)
      Radical anti-Vietnam paper with graphic images
    - Risala ya Wanafunzi Weusi., 1972 March.; 1 item. (Box 140, Folder 15)
      Masthead: "Information of Black students." Student paper published at UCSB
    - San Francisco Bay Guardian (folder 1 of 2)., 1968-1969.; 7 items. (Box 140, Folder 16)
    - San Francisco Bay Guardian (folder 2 of 2)., 1970-1971.; 5 items. (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - San Francisco Observer., 1965.; 2 items. (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - Santa Barbara News & Review., 1972-1973.; 5 items. (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - Socialist Call., 1953.; 1 item. (Box 141, Folder 4)
      Communist newspaper
    - Strike!., 1970 May.; 1 item. (Box 141, Folder 5)
      Anti-Vietnam paper with numerous illustrations and political cartoons
    - Twin Cities Express., 1 item. (Box 141, Folder 6)
    - UCSB Daily Nexus., 1970-1975.; 16 items. (Box 141, Folder 7)
      Student paper
    - UMBC Observer., 1974.; 1 item. (Box 141, Folder 8)
      University of Maryland Baltimore County student paper
    - University Review., 1969 May.; 1 item. (Box 141, Folder 9)
      Intercollegiate literary supplement